https://www.thepacificgroup.com/privacy-policy/

NAVIGATING OUR CLIENTS TO REACH THEIR FINANCIAL GOALS
Your tell us the destination , we chart the course to get you there
PRIVACY POLICY
Last updated: January 09, 2020This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.
We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Interpretation and Definitions
The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions.
The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.
Definitions
For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:
You means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.Company (referred to as either “the Company”, “We”, “Us” or “Our” in this Agreement) refers to Pacific Advisory Capital Group, LLC, 500 S. Grand Avenue, Suite 1650, Los Angeles, CA 90071.Affiliate means an entity that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with a party, where “control” means ownership of 50% or more of the shares, equity interest or other securities entitled to vote for election of directors or other managing authority.Account means a unique account created for You to access our Service or parts of our Service.Website refers to The Pacific Group, accessible from https://thepacificgroup.comService refers to the Website.Country refers to: United StatesService Provider means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the Company, to perform services related to the Service or to assist the Company in analyzing how the Service is used.Third-party Social Media Service refers to any website or any social network website through which a User can log in or create an account to use the Service.Personal Data is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.Cookies are small files that are placed on Your computer, mobile device or any other device by a website, containing the details of Your browsing history on that website among its many uses.Usage Data refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).
Collecting and using your Personal Data
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using Our Service, We may ask You to provide Us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify You. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:Email addressFirst name and last namePhone numberAddress, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, CityUsage DataOther personally identifiable or company information
Home
FAQs
Blogs
Our Firm
Contact
Menu
Home
FAQs
Login
Investment advisory and asset management services are offered by investment adviser representatives (IARs) through Pacific Advisory Capital Group, LLC (PAC), a registered investment adviser. PAC IARs are also, separately and apart from PAC, registered representatives who offer insurance products through Pacific Risk Management Group, PLLC (PRMG), which conducts business as PRMG Risk Management and Insurance Solutions, PLLC in the state of California. PAC does not provide tax or legal advice. Individuals may transact business and/or respond to inquiries only in state(s) in which they are properly qualified. PAC provides services under the DBA of The Pacific Group.Please note that although Pacific Advisory Capital Group, LLC is a “registered investment adviser”, readers should be aware that registration with any securities authority does not imply a certain level of skill or trainingTerms of Service.    Privacy Policy      FINRA BrokerCheck©2020 The Pacific Group. All rights reserved.
